// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question:"If [[3, 2], [2, - 3]] * [[x], [y]] = [[4], [7]] + Ren",
    answer: "(2, - 1)",
    options: [
      "(9, 2)",
      "(2, - 1)",
      "(2, - 1)",
      "(3, - 2)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "if a ne b ne c and [[a, a ^ 2, a ^ 3 - 1], [b, b ^ 2, b ^ 3 - 1], [c, c ^ 2, c ^ 3 - 1]] = 0",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "5",
      "2",
      "0",
      "6",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "(2x + 1)/((x - 1)(x ^ 2 + 1)) = A/(x - 1) + (Bx + c)/(x ^ 2 + 1) + than A + B + c =",
    answer: "1/2",
    options: [
      "1/4",
      "1/3",
      "1/2",
      "1"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "If 3x+4/(x+1)^2(x-1=A/x-1 + B/x+1 + c/(x+1)^2) then A= ",
    answer: "1/4",
    options: [
      "1/4",
      "1",
      "7/4",
      "10/3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "sin^-1 x+ sin^-1 (1-x)=cos^-1x ",
    answer: "[0,1/2]",
    options: [
      "[1,0]",
      "[-1,1]",
      "[0,1/2]",
      "[2,0]"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "sin A+sin B=√ (cosB-cosA)",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "0",
      "2",
      "1",
      "-1"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 7,
    question: "180°<θ<270°,sinθ=-3/5 then cosθ/2 ",
    answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "-1/√ 10",
      "1/√ 10",
      "1/10",
      "10"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In ΔABC if (a-b)^2 cos^2 c/2 + (a+b)^2 sin^2 c/2= ",
    answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "a^2",
      "c^2",
      "b^2",
      "a^2 +b^2"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 9,
    question:"2) If a1, a2, a3 respectively denote the module of the complex numbers. j, 1/3(1+i) and (- 1 + i) then their increasing order is.",
    answer: "a2,a1,a3",
    options: [
      "a1,a2,a3",
      "a2,a1,a3",
      "a3,a2,a1",
      "a3,a1,a2"
    ]
},
 {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The angle between the lines kx+y+9=0,y-3x=4 is 45◦,then the value of 'k' is ",
    answer: "+2",
    options: [
      "4",
      "3",
      "+2",
      "1"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Find the equation of rectangle hyperbola whose focus is the point 1,2 and directrix is the line 3x+4y-5=0",
    answer: "2/25(9x^2+16y^20+24xy-30x-40y+25)",
    options: [
      "1/16(2x^2+4y^2-2xy+16x+30y-25)",
      "9/25(9x^2+16y^20-24xy+30x-40y-25)",
      "2/25(9x^2+16y^20+24xy-30x-40y+25)",
      "8/10(6x^2+3y^2-2xy+30x-20y-30)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "If log(1+x)-2x/2+x is increasing then.",
    answer: "0<X<∞",
    options: [
      "0<X<∞",
      "-∞<x<0",
      "-∞<x<80",
      "1<x<2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "If the relationship between the subnormal and subtangent at any point on the curve by^2=(x+a) is of the form P(S.N)=q(S.T)^2 then P/q=",
    answer: "8b/27",
    options: [
      "8a/27",
      "8b/27",
      "27a/8",
      "27b/8"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "If a particle is moving on a straight line according to the law S=4t^3-6t^2+t-7 then the acceleration of the particle after 2 sec is",
    answer: "36",
    options: [
      "0",
      "18",
      "24",
      "36"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The minimum value of (x-a)(x-ß) is",
    answer: "-1/4(a-ß)^2",
    options: [
      "0",
      "aß",
      "1/4(a-ß)^2",
      "-1/4(a-ß)^2"
    ]
  } 
];